firstshowing.net 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy | FirstShowing.net

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which **FirstShowing.net** collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [www.firstshowing.net](https://www.firstshowing.net/) website ("Site"). This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information received and collected by FirstShowing.net and how it is used.

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

**Non-personal identification information?**  
We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about users means of connection to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the site may not function properly.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information FirstShowing.net collects from a user may be used in one of the following ways:  
» To personalize user experience: We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our site.  
» To improve our site: We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.  
» To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.  
» To send periodic emails: If user decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the user would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our site.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or rent users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Advertising Cookies**  
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**  
Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network Privacy Policy at <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). You can also find out how to opt out of various ad programs at that [link](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

**Some of our advertising partners may use cookies on our site. Our advertising partners include:**  
<https://www.google.com/doubleclick/>  
<https://affiliate-program.amazon.com/>  
<https://freestar.io/>

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. FirstShowing.net's Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**Regarding content copying and duplication**  
All rights reserved exclusively to FirstShowing.net for the content created and posted on this website. We retain all rights to display the text in these posts, and refuse the right of any replication. This means you cannot duplicate or copy posts without our permission. Just because our content is published in our RSS feed or elsewhere in connect with the website, does not mean you can re-post it on any other website. Please do not do this. All of these posts are exclusive to this website and appear here and only here.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
FirstShowing.net has the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**  
By using this site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**  
If you require any more information or have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at:  
First Showing LLC  

_This document was last updated on March 30, 2018_.
